Drink up, me hearties,
yo ho
We kidnap and ravage
and don't give a hoot
Drink up, me hearties,
yo ho
Yo ho, yo ho
A pirate's life for me
We extort, we pilfer,
we filch and sack
Drink up
Quiet, missy.
Cursed pirates sail
these waters.
You don't want to bring them.
Mr. Gibbs, that will do.
She was singing about pirates.
It's bad luck to be singing
about pirates
with us mired
in this unnatural fog.
Mark my words.
Consider them marked.
On your way.
Aye, Lieutenant.
It's bad luck to have
a woman on board, too.
Even a miniature one.
I think it'd be rather exciting
to meet a pirate.
Think again, Miss Swann.
Vile and dissolute creatures,
the lot of them.
I intend that any man
who sails under a pirate flag
or wears a pirate brand gets
what he deserves.
A short drop and a sudden stop.
Lieutenant Norrington,
I appreciate your fervor,
but I' m concerned
about the effect
this subject will have
upon my daughter.
My apologies, Governor Swann.
Actually,
I find it all fascinating.
Yes.
That's what concerns me.
Look! A boy!
There's a boy in the water!
LT. NORRINGTON:
Man overboard!
Man the ropes.
Fetch a hook.
Haul him aboard.
He's still breathing.
Mary, Mother of God.
GO V. SWANN:
What happened here?
It's the powder magazine.
Merchant vessels run
heavily armed.
Alot of good it did them.
Everyone's thinking it.
I'm just saying it.
Pirates.
There's no proof of that.
It's probably an accident.
LT. NORRINGTON:
Rouse the captain immediately.
Heave to and take in sail
Launch the boats.
Elizabeth, I want you
to accompany the boy.
He'll be in your charge.
Take care of him.
It's okay.
My name's Elizabeth Swann.
Will Turner.
I'm watching over you, Will.
You're a pirate.
Has he said anything?
His name's William Turner.
That's all I found out.
Take him below.
Elizabeth?
Are you all right?
Are you decent?
Yes.
Still abed at this hour?
Oh, it's a beautiful day.
I have a gift for you.
Oh, it's beautiful
Isn't it?
May I inquire
as to the occasion?
Does a father need an occasion
to dote upon his daughter?
Go on.
Actually, I...
I hoped you might wear it
for the ceremony today.
The ceremony?
Captain Norrington's
promotion ceremony.
I knew it.
Commodore Norrington,
as he's about to become.
A fine gentleman,
don't you think?
He fancies you, you know.
Elizabeth?
How's it coming?
It's difficult to say.
I'm told it's the latest fashion
in London.
Well, women in London
must've learnt not to breathe.
Milord, you have a visitor.
Mr. Turner.
Good to see you again.
Good day, sir.
I have your order.
Well.
The blade is folded steel
That's gold filigree
laid into the handle.
If I may.
Perfectly balanced.
The tang is nearly
the full width of the blade.
Impressive.
Very impressive.
Now, now.
Commodore Norrington is going
to be very pleased with this.
Do pass my compliments on
to your master.
I shall.
A craftsman is always pleased
to hear his work is appreciated.
Elizabeth,
you look absolutely stunning.
Will.
It's so good to see you.